mypreferredaccount.com 2013-05-16

# Bill Me Later

Website Privacy Statement

Online Consumer Information Practices

Bill Me Later, Inc., Inc., together with WebBank, the parties who offer the Bill Me Later service (collectively, WebBank and Bill Me Later, Inc. are referred to as "Bill Me Later", "we", "us", "our"), are committed to your privacy and security online. We want to satisfy you and provide a superior online experience while respecting your privacy. 

Collection and Use of Information

 **Information you provide.** When you visit our site, we may ask you to "log-in," complete a survey, or answer questions. These may include questions such as where you live, your email address and your interest in receiving email from Bill Me Later on new products and services. We collect this information so that we can determine what kinds of products and services are of most interest to you.

You may register your account online and provide contact information (such as email address) and financial information (such as bank account information) during account registration, which will allow you to service your account online. This information is necessary to enable you to view statements online, review account activity and schedule payments on your Bill Me Later account.

**Information We Gather Automatically.** The site also automatically collects information from users who visit the site. This information includes, but is not limited to: Internet Protocol (IP) address of the user, the browser and version being used by a user, pages visited, date and time each page was accessed, search, browsing and other similar information. We may also use identification information we collect in order to protect against actual or potential fraud.

In addition, we may receive and store certain information whenever you visit the site. In order to constantly improve our web site and better serve our customers online, we may use either cookies or clear gifs or other similar files or tools to obtain certain types of information when you visit the site. Cookies are small data files that we place on your hard drive or web browser memory that store information that enables Bill Me Later, Inc. to provide convenient features, enhance your user experience, and protect against fraud. For example, cookies allow our system to recognize you when you return to the site. Information gathered may include date and time of visits, pages viewed, time spent at the site, and the sites visited just before and just after the Bill Me Later site. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier that function together with cookies and enable us to collect information such as the online movements of users or whether a user has opened an email.

We use both session and persistent cookies when you access our website or content. Session cookies expire and no longer have any effect when you log out of your account or close your browser. Persistent cookies remain on your browser until you erase them or they expire.

We also use Local Shared Objects, commonly referred to as "Flash cookies", to help ensure that your account security is not compromised, to spot irregularities in behavior, to help prevent fraud, and to support our sites and services.

We encode all of our cookies so that only we can interpret the information stored in them. You are free to decline our cookies if your browser or browser add-on permits, but doing so may interfere with your use of our website. Also, the help section of most browsers or browser add-ons provides instructions on blocking, deleting or disabling cookies.

You may encounter Bill Me Later cookies on websites that we do not control. For example, if you view a web page created by a third party or use an application developed by a third party, there may be a cookie placed by the web page or application. Likewise, these third parties may place cookies that are not subject to our control and the Bill Me Later Privacy Statement does not cover their use.

Except as further provided herein, any personal information we receive will not be released to a third party unless in connection with a merger, acquisition, sale, liquidation, reorganization, or other business combination. Information that has been made anonymous so that it does not identify a specific user, is not considered personal information. Notwithstanding the above, Bill Me Later, Inc. will release any information if required by law or valid judicial order without further notice to User.

**Use of Information.** The information we collect from you helps us improve our site and personalize your user experience. The information we collect also helps to mitigate risk, prevent fraud, and promote trust and safety. For example, we may use the information to email you about service updates, improve our services, and determine the content and layout of our site.

**Use of Information for Online Advertising.** We use clear gifs, as well as session and persistent cookies to evaluate our web site and to track (i) advertising leads and campaigns from banner ads, (ii) opt in emails and (iii) third party ad services.

We may hire companies such as third party ad services to track and report performance of advertising and marketing campaigns to and from Bill Me Later and third party web sites. We permit certain of these companies to set cookies and use related technology, such as clear gifs. This information will remain anonymous and your personal information will not be shared. These clear gifs (also known as tracking pixels, action tags, web pixels, or web beacons) and other similar tracking technologies may be used to collect and store information about user visits, such as the user's anonymous cookie ID, page visits and duration, and the specific ad or link(s) that the user clicked on to visit the site. No personally identifiable information is stored on these cookies or clear gifs. This user activity information is reported to us in aggregate and remains anonymous. We use this information in aggregate to understand, for example, the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing.

Email Communications

If you choose to send us an email message, we may retain the content of the email, your email address, and our response in order to service your needs.

We or a third party acting on our behalf, may use the data that you provide to send you email offers that may be of special interest to you. If you unsubscribe from these email messages, you will not receive these messages from Bill Me Later via email. See email Opt Out below for more details.

Please note that some of our services including the Bill Me Later website require a valid email address in order to register and/or continue use of the service. You will receive email alerts or notification messages from these programs unless you un-enroll from these services.

Email Opt Out

If you no longer wish to receive email offers or solicitations from Bill Me Later, you may unsubscribe by following the instructions in the original email you received. The instructions are generally located at the bottom of the email. If you receive emails from third parties or program partners on behalf of Bill Me Later, please be sure to unsubscribe through the instructions in the email or contact these third parties directly.

If you opt out of email solicitations, Bill Me Later reserves the right to contact you via email to service and maintain your account relationship. For example, we may notify you about activity on your account, respond to any customer inquiries or requests, or alert you to web site changes or outages.

Email Tips

Do not provide your email address to third party web sites without reading the privacy and security policies and terms and conditions of these sites to ensure you understand the circumstances in which your email address will be used.

If you suspect suspicious or fraudulent activity related to your account(s), please let your account provider know right away. You should also contact your Internet Service Provider so they may block suspicious messages from your email inbox. To learn more about how to control and manage your incoming emails, please refer to your Internet Service Providers' online resources. You may also visit the Federal Trade Commission's web site on spam at [www.ftc.gov/spam](http://www.ftc.gov/spam).

Links to Third Party Sites

Bill Me Later is not responsible for the information practices employed by sites linked to or from our web site. In most cases, links to non-Bill Me Later web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of the Bill Me Later web site. Since third party web sites may have different privacy policies and/or security standards governing their sites, we advise you to review the privacy policies and terms and conditions of these sites prior to providing any personal information.

Children's Online Privacy

Protecting children on the Internet is very important to us. For that reason, Bill Me Later does not intentionally collect information at our web sites from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our web site is intended to attract anyone under 13. Parents can be proactive and limit web site access to their children by installing filtering software.

**Children's access to the Internet can permit them to visit inappropriate web sites and be exposed to unnecessary risks. The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) protects children under the age of 13 from the online collection of personal information. Learn more about COPPA at the Federal Trade Commission's web site for children's privacy at<http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens_educ.html> and by viewing the following link on [How to Protect Kids' Privacy Online](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/consumer/tech/tec08.shtm).**

May 2012

Bill Me Later Account Privacy Policy

**WebBank Privacy Statement**

rev. July 2011

FACTS | **WHAT DOES WEBBANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR BILL ME LATER ACCOUNT?**  
---|---  
Why? | Financial companies choose how they share your personal information.  Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing.  Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information.  Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
---|---  
What? | The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

**•** Social Security number and income  
**•** Account balance and transaction history  
**•** Credit history and credit score. 

When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.   
  
---|---  
How? | All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business.  In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons WebBank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
---|---  
**Reasons we can share your personal information** | **Does WebBank share?** | **Can you limit this sharing?**  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes**  
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus | 

Yes

| No  
**For our marketing purposes**  
To offer our products and services to you | Yes | No  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies** | Yes | No  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes**  
information about your transactions and experiences | No | We don't share  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes**  
information about your creditworthiness | No | We don't share  
**For our affiliates to market to you** | No | We don't share  
**For non-affiliated companies to market to you** | No | We don't share  
**Questions?** | Call: 866-528-3733  
---|---  
  
**-Page 2-**

Who we are  
---  
  
**Who is providing this notice?**

| 

WebBank  
  
What we do  
---  
  
**How does WebBank protect my personal information?**

| 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.  These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.  
  
**How does WebBank collect my personal information?**

| 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you:

**•** Open an account or use your account  
**•** Pay your bill or give us your contact information  
**•** Provide account information

We also collect your personal information from others such as credit bureaus, affiliates, and other companies.  
  
**Why can't I limit all sharing?**

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only:

**•** sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes information about your creditworthiness  
**•** affiliates from using your information to market to you  
**•** sharing for non-affiliated companies to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.  
  
**What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?**

| 

We do not have joint accounts.  
  
Definitions  
---  
  
**Affiliates**

| 

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.  
**•** _WebBank does not share with affiliates._  
  
**Non-affiliated Companies**

| 

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.  
**•** _WebBank does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you._  
  
**Joint Marketing**

| 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.   
**•** _Our joint marketing partners include financial companies such as banks or insurers._  
  
**Other Important Information**  
---  
If you live in Vermont, we will not share information about your creditworthiness with our affiliates for their everyday business purposes unless you consent to that sharing. If you live in California, we will not share information about you (1) with our affiliates for their own purposes or (2) for joint marketing with other financial companies.  
  
**Bill Me Later, Inc. Privacy Statement**

rev. July 2011

FACTS | **WHAT DOES BILL ME LATER, INC. (Servicer) DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR BILL ME LATER ACCOUNT**?  
---|---  
Why? | Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
---|---  
What? | The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

**•** Social Security number and income  
**•** Account balance and transaction history  
**•** Credit history and credit score.   
  
---|---  
How? | All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Bill Me Later, Inc. chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
---|---  
**Reasons we can share your personal information** | **Does Bill Me Later, Inc. share?** | **Can you limit this sharing?**  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes**  
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus | 

Yes

| No  
**For our marketing purposes**  
To offer our products and services to you | Yes | No  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies** | Yes | No  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes**  
information about your transactions and experiences | Yes | No  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes**  
information about your creditworthiness | Yes | Yes  
**For our affiliates to market to you** | Yes | Yes  
**For non-affiliated companies to market to you** | No | We don't share  
To limit our sharing |  **•** Call 866-528-3733 - our menu will prompt you through your choice(s) or  
**•** Visit us online at: [www.billmelater.com/about/privacy_policy.xhtml](https://www.billmelater.com/your-account/privacy-policy-opt-out.xhtml)  
**Please note:**   
If you are a new customer, with respect to those circumstances in which you can limit our sharing, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.

However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.  
  
---|---  
  
**-Page 4-**

Who we are  
---  
  
**Who is providing this notice?**

| 

Bill Me Later, Inc. (Servicer)  
  
What we do  
---  
  
**How does Bill Me Later protect my personal information?**

| 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.  
  
**How does Bill Me Later collect my personal information?**

| 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you:

**•** Open an account or use your account  
**•** Pay your bill or give us your contact information  
**•** Provide account information

We also collect your personal information from others such as credit bureaus, affiliates, and other companies.  
  
**Why can't I limit all sharing?**

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only:

**•** sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes information about your creditworthiness  
**•** affiliates from using your information to market to you  
**•** sharing for non-affiliated companies to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.  
  
**What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?**

| 

We do not have joint accounts.  
  
Definitions  
---  
  
**Affiliates**

| 

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.  
**•** _Bill Me Later, Inc.'s affiliates include financial companies such as PayPal and nonfinancial companies such as eBay._  
  
**Non-affiliated Companies**

| 

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.  
**•** _Bill Me Later, Inc. does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you._  
  
**Joint Marketing**

| 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.   
**•** _Our joint marketing partners include financial companies such as banks or insurers._  
  
**Other Important Information**  
---  
If you live in Vermont, we will not share information about your creditworthiness with our affiliates for their everyday business purposes unless you consent to that sharing. If you live in California, we will not share information about you (1) with our affiliates for their own purposes or (2) for joint marketing with other financial companies.
